[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "What is the national animal of Canada?",
   "Answer": "North American beaver"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "What is the national animal of Albania?",
   "Answer": "Golden eagle"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "Which dog used to be sacred in China?",
   "Answer": "Pekingese"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "Urticaria is a skin disease otherwise known as what?",
   "Answer": "Hives"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "What kind of animal is the largest living creature on Earth",
   "Answer": "Whale"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "Give another name for the study of fossils?",
   "Answer": "Paleontology"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Which bird can swim but cannot fly?",
   "Answer": "Penguin"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "What do dragonflies prefer to eat?",
   "Answer": "Mosquitoes"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "What do you get when you crossbreed a donkey and a horse?",
   "Answer": "Hinny"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "Which insects cannot fly, but can jump higher than 30 cm?",
   "Answer": "Fleas"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the European Bison?",
   "Answer": "Wisent"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "What is called a fish with a snake-like body?",
   "Answer": "Eel fish"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "In which city is the oldest zoo in the world?",
   "Answer": "Vienna"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "After which animals are the Canary Islands named?",
   "Answer": "Dogs"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "Which plant does the Canadian flag contain?",
   "Answer": "Maple"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "What is the food of penguins?",
   "Answer": "Plankton"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "Which is the largest species of the tiger?",
   "Answer": "Siberian tiger"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "The bite of which insect causes the Lyme Disease?",
   "Answer": "Deer Tick"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "Which mammal cannot jump?",
   "Answer": "Elephant"
 }
]